### Contact

ayush.soni206@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ayush-soni-040356125 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Machine Learning
Data Science
Python

### Certifications

Getting Started with AWS Machine Learning

# Ayush Soni

Data Scientist at Xalt Analytics Indore

## Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the management consulting industry. Skilled in Statistical Data Analysis, Statistical Modeling, Communication, Data Science, and Corporate Communications. Strong engineering professional graduated from IPS ACADEMY, Indore.

## Experience

Xalt Analytics
Data Scientist
September 2018 - Present (2 years)
Indore, Madhya Pradesh, India

#### **AVL**

Trainee Data Scientist
February 2018 - September 2018 (8 months)
Indore

## Education

IPS ACADEMY, Indore

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science · (2014 - 2018)